Martin P. Catherwood Library Exchange Bibliographies /4035
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin P. Catherwood Library Exchange Bibliographies
1947-1968
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
Martin P. Catherwood Library
/4035
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents), bibliographies.
3084917
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 02, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 21, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Martin P. Catherwood Library.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
3084917
- Bibliography: ILR Publications in the Public Employee Relations Field - 11/68 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Selected Readings Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 2)
- List of Material Published by the NYS ILR School, July 1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Field Guide to Exchange Bibliographies (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Exchange Bibliographies - Cornell List No. 1, Labor Union Political Action (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Exchange Bibliographies - Cornell List No. 2, Labor and the 1948 Political Campaign (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Exchange Bibliographies - Cornell List No. 3, Profit Sharing (Box 1, Folder 7)
- ILR at General, Cornell List No. 4 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Labor Condi and Problems in American Agriculture, Cornell List No. 5 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Promotions and Transfers - Cornell List No. 6 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Conference Technique - Cornell List No. 7, October 1948 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Labor Participation in Management, Cornell List No. 8 - October 1948 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Merit Rating, Cornell List No. 9 - October 1948 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Job Evaluation, Cornell List No. 10 - October 1948 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- American Trade Union Histories, Cornell No. 12 - October 1948 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Taft-Hartley Act, Cornell No. 13 - October 1947 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Safety Education in VOC1 and Industrial School Shops, Cornell List No. 14 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Wage Incentives, Cornell List No. 16 - February 1950 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Foreman Compensation, Cornell No. 17 - December 1949 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Management Prerogative Issue, Cornell 18 - Nov. 1949 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Workers Education, Cornell 19 - June 1949 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Collective Bargaining, Cornell 20 - April 1948 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Labor Law General, Cornell 22, February 1949 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Labor Turnover, Cornell 23 - February 1949 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Employee Selection and Placement, Cornell 24 - February 1949 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Industrial Psychology, Cornell 25 - January 1950 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Functions of a Personnel Department, Cornell 26 - January 1950 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Training Distributive Occupations, Cornell 27 - March 1949 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Municipal Labor Management Relations, Cornell 28 - May 1949 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Labor Arbitration, Cornell 29 - September 1949 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Labor Relations in Relating: Sources of Info, Cornell 30 - October 1949 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Recent Labor Union History - October 1949 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Office Production and Status Reports - October 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Materials for an Industrial Relations Seminar Library - October 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Unionization of Professional Workers - October 1949 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Union Health and Welfare Plans - October 1949 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Personnel Management - September 1949 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Picketing - January 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Case Books on Labor Law - July 1950 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Recruiting and Development of Executives - March 1951 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Personnel Department Records and Organization - March 1951 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- The Work Week - May 1951 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Foreman - June 1951 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Workers Education in the US - September 1950 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Employability of the Older Worker (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Labor Relations Law - July 1950 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Labor Law - February 1950 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Labor Union History - March 1951 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Exchange Bibliographies Fact Finding (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Foreman (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Exchange Bibliographies, The Work Week (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Selected List of Periodicals for a Plant Training Library (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Jurisdictional Disputes (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Labor Union History (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Labor Problems (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Organizations and Trade Associations Publishing Material Dealing with In-Plant Training (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Personnel Administration (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Personnel Department - Records and Organization (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Recruiting and Development of Executives (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Unemployment (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Union Shop (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Multiple Management (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Employee Benefits (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Exchange Bibliographies, The Work Week (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Exchange Bibliographies, ILR Bookshelf for YMCA Secretaries (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Recruiting at Colleges and Universities (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Induction and Training of New Employees (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Fact Finding (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Foreman (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Communication in Industry (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Vestibule Training (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Employment of Older and Disabled Workers (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Exchange Bibliographies, The Scanlon Plan (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Seniority Promotion and Layoff (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Absenteeism and Turnover (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Longshore Industry with Emphasis on the Situation in NYC (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Arbitration of Labor Disputes in Certain Countries (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Labor Journalism (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Organizations Actively Opposing Discrimination in Employment (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Employment of Negroes (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Exchange Bibliographies - Labor Unions in Government (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Exchange Bibliographies - Mediation (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Exchange Bibliographies - Awards in the Fields of Industrial Relations, Industrial Management, and Education (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Desk Books for the Newspaperman (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Exchange Bibliographies - Recruiting at Colleges and Universities (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Democracy in Unions and Responsibilities of Union Officers to their Members (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Labor's Position in Relation to Education (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Exchange Bibliographies, General Management Problems (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Wage Incentives (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Seniority Promotion and Layoff (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Collective Bargaining by Public Employees (Box 1, Folder 91)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Employee Benefits (Box 1, Folder 92)
- Exchange Bibliographies, The Scanlon Plan (Box 1, Folder 93)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Employment of Older and Disabled Workers (Box 1, Folder 94)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Taft-Hartley Amendments (Box 1, Folder 95)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Executive Development (Box 1, Folder 96)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Text for Industrial and Labor Relations (Box 1, Folder 97)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Industrial Safety (Box 1, Folder 98)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Retirement Systems (Box 1, Folder 99)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Labor Unions-Communism (Box 1, Folder 100)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Foreman and Supervisors-Selection (Box 1, Folder 101)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Workmen's Compensation (Box 1, Folder 102)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Labor Participation in Management (Box 1, Folder 103)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Personnel Selection and Placement (Box 1, Folder 104)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Industrial Psychiatry (Box 1, Folder 105)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Communism in Labor Unions (Box 1, Folder 106)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Work Simplification (Box 1, Folder 107)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Selected Bibliographies and Indexes in ILR (Box 1, Folder 108)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Evaluating Conferences (Box 1, Folder 109)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Labor Unions (Box 1, Folder 110)
- Exchange Bibliographies, List of Serial Publications Currently Received from India, Pakistan and Ceylon (Box 1, Folder 111)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Public Relations (Box 1, Folder 112)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Dismissal Wage (Box 1, Folder 113)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Industrial Psychology for Supervisors (Box 1, Folder 114)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Selected Materials on Leadership Development (Box 1, Folder 115)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Industrial Relations Libraries (Box 1, Folder 116)
- Preparation for Retirement (Box 1, Folder 117)
- Employment of Older and Disabled Workers (Box 1, Folder 118)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Management Strategy and Tactics in Collective Bargaining (Box 1, Folder 119)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Discrimination in Employment (Box 1, Folder 120)
- Bibliographies, Special Bibliographies and Indexes in ILR (Box 1, Folder 121)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Bibliography on Personnel Administration (Box 1, Folder 122)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Management Cooperation (Box 1, Folder 123)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Labor Movements in Latin America Philippines India and Japan (Box 1, Folder 124)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Workmen's Compensation (Box 1, Folder 125)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Absenteeism (Box 1, Folder 126)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Human Relations in Industry (Box 1, Folder 127)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Training Foremen and Supervisors (Box 1, Folder 128)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Fair Labor Standards Act (Box 1, Folder 129)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Selected Texts for ILR (Box 1, Folder 130)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Seniority Promotion and Layoff (Box 1, Folder 131)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Industrial Safety (Box 1, Folder 132)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Labor Turnover (Box 1, Folder 133)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Foremen and Supervisors Selection (Box 1, Folder 134)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Work Satisfaction (Box 1, Folder 135)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Grievance Handling (Box 1, Folder 136)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Employing the Handicapped (Box 1, Folder 137)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Recent Selected References (Box 1, Folder 138)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Negroes Labor Unions (Box 1, Folder 139)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Selected References (Box 1, Folder 140)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Business and Politics (Box 1, Folder 141)
- Exchange Bibliographies, Discrimination in Employment (Box 1, Folder 142)
- Exchange Bibliographies: Supplemental Unemployment Benefits (Box 1, Folder 143)
- Exchange Bibliographies: Stock Ownership Plans, Recent References (Box 1, Folder 144)
- Exchange Bibliographies: Engineers and Scientists (Box 1, Folder 145)
- Exchange Bibliographies: Communication in Industry, Recent References (Box 1, Folder 146)
- Exchange Bibliographies: Training of Shop Stewards, Recent References (Box 1, Folder 147)
- Exchange Bibliographies: Personnel Administration in Hospitals (Box 1, Folder 148)
- Exchange Bibliographies: Shop Stewards (Box 1, Folder 149)
- Exchange Bibliographies: Executive Development (Box 1, Folder 150)
- Exchange Bibliographies: Management Rights and Responsibilities (Box 1, Folder 151)
- Exchange Bibliographies: Selected List of General Works on Personnel Administration (Box 1, Folder 152)
- Exchange Bibliographies: Labor Relations in Public Employment (Box 1, Folder 153)
- Exchange Bibliographies: Selected Readings in Hospital Administration (Box 1, Folder 154)
- Exchange Bibliographies: Selected Readings on the Unionization of Public School Teachers (Box 1, Folder 155)
- Exchange Bibliographies: Basic Readings in Labor-Management (Box 1, Folder 156)
- Exchange Bibliography: Readings on Labor Monopoly (Box 1, Folder 157)
- Exchange Bibliography: Workers Attitudes Towards Union (Box 1, Folder 158)
- Exchange Bibliography: Readings on Job Evaluation (Box 1, Folder 159)
- Exchange Bibliography: Labor Unions Rights and Responsibilities (Box 1, Folder 160)
- Exchange Bibliography: Readings in the History of British Trade Unionism (Box 1, Folder 161)
- Exchange Bibliography: Selected Readings on Problems of the Aging (Box 1, Folder 162)
- Exchange Bibliography: Selected References on Union Organizing (Box 1, Folder 163)
- Exchange Bibliography: Preparing for Collective Bargaining (Box 1, Folder 164)
- Exchange Bibliography: A Selected List of Readings on Absenteeism (Box 1, Folder 165)
- Exchange Bibliography: Readings on Labor Relations in Public Employment (Box 1, Folder 166)
- Exchange Bibliography: Readings on International Labor (Box 1, Folder 167)
- Exchange Bibliography: Labor Relations in the Maritime Industry (Box 1, Folder 168)
- Exchange Bibliography: Personnel Management Activities (Box 1, Folder 169)
- Exchange Bibliography: Objectives and Methods in Management Development (Box 1, Folder 170)
- Exchange Bibliography: Apprenticeship (Box 1, Folder 171)
- Exchange Bibliography: Wage Incentives (Box 1, Folder 172)
- Exchange Bibliography: Medical Care and Social Security (Box 1, Folder 173)
- Exchange Bibliography: More Selected References on Union Organization (Box 1, Folder 174)
- Exchange Bibliography: Communication in Industry (Box 1, Folder 175)
- Exchange Bibliography: Vacations (Box 1, Folder 176)
- Exchange Bibliography: Discrimination in Employment (Box 1, Folder 177)
- Exchange Bibliography: Readings on Wages and Prices (Box 1, Folder 178)
- Exchange Bibliography: Seniority, Promotion, and Layoff (Box 1, Folder 179)
- Exchange Bibliography: Selected Readings on Unemployment with Emphasis on Frictional Unemployment (Box 1, Folder 180)
- Exchange Bibliography: Readings on Wage and Prices (Box 1, Folder 181)
- Exchange Bibliography: Union Welfare Funds and Collective Bargaining (Box 1, Folder 182)
- Exchange Bibliography: Counseling Techniques and Procedures (Box 1, Folder 183)
- Exchange Bibliography: Labor Relations in the Construction Industry (Box 1, Folder 184)
- Exchange Bibliography: Supervisory and Non-Supervisory Personnel (Box 1, Folder 185)
- Exchange Bibliography: Selected Readings on Recruiting (Box 1, Folder 186)
- Exchange Bibliography: Selected References on Labor Law (Box 1, Folder 187)
- Exchange Bibliography: Communication in Industry (Box 1, Folder 188)
- Exchange Bibliography: Supervisory Training Programs (Box 1, Folder 189)
- Exchange Bibliogrpahy: Hiring, Development, and Promoting Negro Employees (Box 1, Folder 190)
- Exchange Bibliography: Utilization of Womanpower (Box 1, Folder 191)
- Exchange Bibliography: White Collar Worker - Labor Unions (Box 1, Folder 192)
- Exchange Bibliography: History of the Unionization of Federal Employees (Box 1, Folder 193)
- Exchange Bibliography: Strikes and Strike Experience of Public Employees (Box 1, Folder 194)
- Exchange Bibliography: Role Playing (Box 1, Folder 195)
- Exchange Bibliography: Management of Professional Personnel (Box 1, Folder 196)
- Exchange Bibliography: The Historical Role of the Negro in the Labor Movement (Box 1, Folder 197)
- Exchange Bibliography: Selected Readings on the Professional and his Union (Box 1, Folder 198)
- Exchange Bibliography: Selected Readings on Permanent Arbitrators (Box 1, Folder 199)
- Exchange Bibliography: Selected Readings on Executive Order (Box 1, Folder 200)
- Exchange Bibliography: Selected Readings on Mental Health Insurance (Box 1, Folder 201)
- Exchange Bibliography: Selected Readings on Collective Bargaining for Employees of Voluntary and Proprietary Hospitals (Box 1, Folder 202)
- Compulsory Arbitration: Selected Readings (Box 1, Folder 203)
- Exchange Bibliography: Selected Readings on Industrial Relations in the Railroad Industry (Box 1, Folder 204)
- Exchange Bibliography: The Negro Revolution and Riots (Box 1, Folder 205)
- Exchange Bibliography: The Negro Revolution and the Labor Movement Today (Box 1, Folder 206)
- Exchange Bibliography: The Negro Revolution (Box 1, Folder 207)
- Exchange Bibliography: Selected Readings on Employment Opportunities for Older Workers (Box 1, Folder 208)
- Exchange Bibliography: Selected Readings on Impact of Labor Unions on Wages (Box 1, Folder 209)